# **Heather Storseth**

| Holland, MI 49423 |

| Email: heatherstorseth3@gmail.com | Phone: (509) 901-1565 | LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/heather-storseth/ | GitHub: https://github.com/ | Portfolio: https://hstor3.github.io/react-portfolio/

## **Summary**

Full stack web developer with a background in child development. Ability to learn new skills quickly, proves capable of taking on higher roles, and possesses the power to patiently teach children and adults of all ages. Meticulous multitasker that's ready to solve any unexpected problems. Expert organizer who's able to implement creative ideas on how to stay organized/improve.

#### **Technical Skills**

JavaScript, JQuery, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Node.js, React.js, Express.js, MySQL, MongoDB, Heroku, Cache, GSAP, PWAs, Git, Handlebars.js

## **Projects**

#### Wall-Pro MPP

Built With: React, Express, Sequelize, CSS, JavaScript, Node, Heroku, MySQL

Repo: <a href="https://github.com/mbussert/shaw-ppc">https://github.com/mbussert/shaw-ppc</a>

Deployed: <a href="http://www.wallpro.net/">http://www.wallpro.net/</a>

This app allows clients to calculate the linear square footage for vinyl installation and submit as many orders as needed to the design company. The administrators are able to view completed orders and orders that need to be completed.

### **MVC Blog**

Built With: Handlebars, Express, Sequelize, CSS, JavaScript, Node, Heroku, MySQL

Repo: <a href="https://github.com/hstor3/turtle-sniffles">https://github.com/hstor3/turtle-sniffles</a>

Deployed: <a href="https://warm-bayou-06994.herokuapp.com/">https://warm-bayou-06994.herokuapp.com/</a>

This app allows users to add a post to the blog, comment on posts, and delete posts and comments.

#### **Workout Tracker**

Built With: MongoDB, Express, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node, Heroku

Repo: <a href="https://github.com/hstor3/potato-tracker">https://github.com/hstor3/potato-tracker</a>

Deployed: https://protected-river-09385.herokuapp.com/

Allows a user to log their cardio/resistance workouts and keep track of their progress with a bar and line graph.

## Experience

Nanny, Grand Rapids, MI — Nanny Extraordinaire — August 2016 - March 2019

Sustaining a relationship with the parents, exposing the children to new activities and educating them along the way, keeping up with minimal household chores, arranging playdates

Whistle Stop Child Development Center, Grand Rapids, MI — Lead Teacher — August 2015 - August 2016

Maintaining a mentally organized work environment for my assistants and students. Responsible for making sure assistants were trained, out on time, classroom cleaned, myself and assistants were maintaining a positive relationship with parents and meeting their goals for their children, and assigning tasks to volunteer assistants with disabilities.

AppleTree Early Care/Preschool, Grand Rapids, MI — *Team Lead & Lead Teacher* — July 2014 - July 2015 Responsibilities include, lesson planning, maintaining a relationship with parents and meeting goals for their children, training new staff members, supervising four classrooms and associated staff members. Ensured that staff clocked out on time and in order, classrooms were clean at the end of day, keeping count of the number of children in each room and the building, rotating toys/books amongst rooms, and assigning tasks to the staff.

#### Education

Full Stack Flex Coding Bootcamp Certificate — Michigan State University — January 2021-July 2021